

Ostap Klysa Frontend Developer (Junior)

About me

I am Ostap Klysa, a web developer from Porto, Portugal. I am passionate about technology, art design and above all I love coding and develop new projects. Some of the tools I use to express myself through coding are HTML, CSS/SASS, JavaScript but I am always searching and learning new technologies to improve myself. I have experience designing and developing Web applications from **backend side**, using **Laravel framework** with a powerful CMS called OctoberCMS, to the frontend side using mostly web tools and frameworks such as HTML, CSS/SASS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, to name a few.

Age 24 Contacts

Number +351 937373213

Email ostapklysa@gmail.com

Hobbies

Developing personal projects Listening music Car Enthusiast

My Skills

9.5 / 10

Css/Sass 9 / 10

5 / 10

Bootstrap 3/4/5

8 / 10

TailwindCss

HTML

JS

October CMS

(Creating simple sites with backoffice 'Blog', 'Product portfolio').

Work experience with Razor Pages in ASP.NET Core. (Creation of the visual part for exist Razor Pages Backend in Visual Studio).

Fast adaptation to a new project or an existing one.

Understanding splicing frontend from backend (CMS Frameworks, excluding Wordpress).

Work experience

Freelance (12.2019 - present time).

Junta Digital Production (03.2017 - 11.2019).

- Responsive
- Css/Sass/Scss
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript/Jquery
- October CMS
- In 2018 responsible for Front-End (project creation, project structure, some project planning, time estimate)

Basepoint (internship) (10.2016 - 12.2016).

- Responsive
- Css
- JavaScript

Engetec (internship) (5.2014 - 07.2014).

- Diagnostic (Desktops & Laptops)
- Repairs Software e Hardware

Knowledge

Git

Terminal

Linux (terminal navigate and use as a workspace).

Slack

Adobe XD

Figma

Avocode

Invision Studio

Trello (Project tracking).

JIRA (Sourcetree App, Issue & Project tracking).

Education

Curso web developer CESAE (06.2016 - 12.2016).

- CSS
- JavaScript

Curso web developer CESAE (06.2016 - 12.2016).

Técnico de Gestão Informatica.

My works (most popular)



















